var questions = [
  {
      "question": "Which of the following levels best represents the military classification system?",
      "option1": "Confidential, private, sensitive, and public",
      "option2": "Top secret, secret, private, sensitive, and public",
      "option3": "Top secret, confidential, private, sensitive, and unclassified",
      "option4": "Top secret, secret, confidential, sensitive and unclassified",
      "answer": 4
  },

  {
      "question": "Which of the following standards describes how well a system or process is documented?",
      "option1": "ISO 27001",
      "option2": "ISO 9001",
      "option3": "ISO 27002",
      "option4": "ISO 17799",
      "answer": 2
  },
{
      "question": "Which of the following endpoint security controls could have been used to potentially prevent malware such as Stuxnet, Conficker and Flame? ",
      "option1": "Implementing disk encryption",
      "option2": "Hardening edge devices",
      "option3": "blocking removable media",
      "option4": "Enforcing application whitelisting",
      "answer": 3
  },
{
      "question": "Place the following in their proper order: ",
      "option1": "Determine SLE, ARO and ALE, then asset value",
      "option2": "Determine asset value, then ARO, SLE and ALE",
      "option3": "Determine asset value, then SLE, ALE, and SLE",
      "option4": "Determine asset value, then SLE, ARO and ALE",
      "answer": 4
  },
{ 
      "question": "The downside of performing this type of assessment is that you are not working with dollar values, so it is sometimes harder to communicate the results of the assemssment to management. Which of the following assessment types does this describe? ",
      "option1": "Qualitative",
      "option2": "Quantitative",
      "option3": "Numeric mitigation",
      "option4": "Red team",
      "answer": 1
  },

{ 
      "question": "Which of the following categories of control can include the logical mechanisms used to control access and authenticate users? ",
      "option1": "Administrative",
      "option2": "Clerical",
      "option3": "technical",
      "option4": "Physical",
      "answer": 3
  },
{ 
      "question": "Which of the following is incorrect when describing an SED? ",
      "option1": "Eases compliance",
      "option2": "Slow performance",
      "option3": "Ease of use",
      "option4": "Strong security",
      "answer": 2
  },
{ 
      "question": "Which of the following is the top level of protection for commercial business classification ",
      "option1": "Secret",
      "option2": "Confidential",
      "option3": "Top secret ",
      "option4": "Private",
      "answer": 2
  },
{ 
      "question": "Which of the following is the most specific of security documents ",
      "option1": "Procedures",
      "option2": "Standards",
      "option3": "Policies ",
      "option4": "Baselines",
      "answer": 1
  },
{ 
      "question": "The last thing you want in an organization is that everyone is accountable but no one is responsible. Therefore, the data owner should be in which of the following groups? ",
      "option1": "End users",
      "option2": "Technical managers",
      "option3": "Senior management ",
      "option4": "Everyone is responsible, therefore all groups are owners ",
      "answer": 3
  },

{ 
      "question": "Which term best describes a symbol, word, name, sound, or thing that uniquely identifies a product or service? ",
      "option1": "Trade secret",
      "option2": "Copyright",
      "option3": "Patent ",
      "option4": "Trademark ",
      "answer": 4
  },
{ 
      "question": "After opening a new branch in the Midwest your company is analyzing buying patterns to determine the relationship between various items purcheased. Which of the following best describes this situation? ",
      "option1": "Data mining",
      "option2": "Knowledge management",
      "option3": "Data warehouse ",
      "option4": "Data standards ",
      "answer": 1
  },
{ 
      "question": "Which ISO document is used for a standard for information security management? ",
      "option1": "ISO 27001",
      "option2": "ISO 27002",
      "option3": "ISO 27004 ",
      "option4": "ISO 27799 ",
      "answer": 3
  },
{ 
      "question": "Which of the following SAN solutions is fast, rides on top of Ethernet, yet is non-routable? ",
      "option1": "SCSI",
      "option2": "iSCSI",
      "option3": "HBA ",
      "option4": "FCoE ",
      "answer": 4
  },
{ 
      "question": "Who is ultimately responsible for the security of an asset? ",
      "option1": "Asset owner",
      "option2": "Auditor",
      "option3": "Custodian ",
      "option4": "Risk assessment team",
      "answer": 1
  },










  


  ]
